<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Discover Horoscope</string>
    <string name="aries">ARIES</string>
    <string name="duration_aries">Mar 21 - Apr 20</string>
    <string name="taurus">TAURUS</string>
    <string name="duration_taurus">Apr 21 - May 21</string>
    <string name="gemini">GEMINI</string>
    <string name="duration_gimini">May 22 - June 21</string>
    <string name="cancer">CANCER</string>
    <string name="duration_cancer">June 22 - July 22</string>
    <string name="libra">LIBRA</string>
    <string name="duration_libra">Sept 23 - Oct 22</string>
    <string name="scorpio">SCORPIO</string>
    <string name="duration_scorpio">Oct 23 - Nov 21</string>
    <string name="leo">LEO</string>
    <string name="duration_leo">July 23 - Aug 22</string>
    <string name="virgo">VIRGO</string>
    <string name="duration_virgo">Aug 23 - Sept 22</string>
    <string name="capricorn">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="duration_capricorn">Dec 22 - Jan 20</string>
    <string name="aquarius">AQUARIUS</string>
    <string name="duration_aquarius">Jan 21 - Feb 19</string>
    <string name="pisces">PISCES</string>
    <string name="duration_pisces">Feb 20 - Mar 20</string>
    <string name="saggitarius">SAGITTARIUS</string>
    <string name="duration_sagittarius">Nov 23 - Dec 21</string>
    <string name="horoscope_view">ARIES</string>
    <string name="lbl_www_discoveritech_com">https://discoveritech.com/</string>
    <string name="aries_one">Learn to exercise control over unwanted expenses in business. Salaried employees may get transferred to their desired location.\n\nBusinesses related to iron, steel, aluminium and other metals will make a substantial amount of progress. Every moment that you spend with your loved one is going to be unforgettable. Atmosphere within the family will be pleasant. Your popularity amongst friends will increase. Be careful with regards to your health during long distance business tours. There may be an occasional burning sensation within the body or an itchy skin condition. Avoid eating junk food. This will be the week when all your hard work will be financially rewarded! Payment dues that had been stuck up since a long time will be realised. Students pursuing higher education will excel.\n\nA lot of hard work will be required to obtain desired results in competitive exams. Students should learn to keep company of friends who are hardworking and focused</string>
    <string name="aries_two">You will feel vulnerable and you will express this intensely. You prefer being isolated, in order to feel safe and calm. Spend some time with your partner or your collaborations, making the atmosphere more pleasant. You will find the emotional strength and resilience required to overcome the difficulties. Calmness and self-control will help you deal with your affairs.\n\nYou should be forthcoming with your partner and avoid trying to control them. You will have a tendency to become demanding, thus shaking the balance in your relationship. No need to worry; you will soon regain your confidence and composure and your relationship will regain its balance. The weekend is a good time for discussions and for setting things straight, with realism and understanding.\n\nPositive developments lie ahead. You will use creative imagination to decompress, to find alternatives and make any manoeuvres necessary. Thus, stress and pressure will be expressed in a creative and productive manner. Your smart ideas will find the ground to grow on. Regarding your finances, it is time to sort things out and make decisions that will lead you safely to improvement.</string>
    <string name="taurus_one">Excellent news in regards to business is expected. Exporting your products will be very beneficial. A slack and non-cooperative attitude from your colleagues will overburden you with work.\n\nYou will be busy with frequent touring. Every evening that you pass with your beloved will simply be unforgettable! Take adequate care of your spouse health. All your relatives and siblings will extend their wholehearted support for your professional growth. You may be troubled by body ache, especially during the night time. Beware! You will be prone to seasonal viral infections during this week. You should plan upon investing your money for the long term by purchasing stocks of a company that has strong fundamentals. Uncontrolled expenses will certainly cause a negative pressure upon your budget. Students will have an un-quenching thirst for knowledge.\n\nThose pursuing higher education will need to work exceptionally hard. Students pursuing creative fields such as jewellery designing and architecture shall excel.</string>
    <string name="taurus_two">The needs of your loves ones become your top priority and you feel a need to get rid of anything that is not useful in your life. This attitude will help you progress and, at the same time, assess your emotional needs and the degree to which they are satisfied. Your thoughts gain structure and order, giving you a rational way of thinking. This is a good time to make decisions.\n\nThis week will be very interesting for your love life, as you approach your inner world and do some soul-searching. Be honest with yourself and your partner, but do not allow your emotions to take you to a place of extreme reactions and behaviors. Be prepared to face sudden surprises, changes and discoveries. Your love life gets better, especially if you are single. It is a very good period for you to make an interesting new acquaintance, or even a new relationship.\n\nUnexpected and pleasant changes are ahead of you. You obtain a new point of view, relieved from stress and insecurity. Instead of adding fuel to the fire, devote your energy to improving any problematic relationships with your colleagues. Approach your finances in a rational manner.</string>
    <string name="gemini_one">Rapid business expansion will call for frequent touring. Manufacturers will successfully be able to supply their products to existing clients as well as new clients. Brokerage or commission businesses will also prosper.\n\nStudents will know their priorities and will remain focused. Teachers and mentors will be full of appreciation for them. They will be able to perform outstandingly well in any competitive examinations. You will enjoy a picnic with your close friends. If you have been waiting to propose to your loved one, this is the time to do it! You will be inclined towards practicing pranayam and yoga which will relax you mentally as well as physically. The week is full of energy and enthusiasm.\n\nYou will spend a substantial amount of money towards purchasing expensive paraphernalia. You will successfully be able to control unnecessary expenses. Salaried employees could be offered an increment in salary or even a promotion.</string>
    <string name="gemini_two"><![CDATA[Emotional tension with someone or something is quite likely, so be prepared and deal with things as calmly as possible. Changes might occur, in an unexpected and eccentric manner. You are quite tired of the same routine, so you will receive these changes happily.\n\nThis week will bring some tension in your relationship. You will be quite charged emotionally, so you had better be open with your partner. Talk to them honestly and try to take their needs into account. Near the end of the week, differences are toned down and you are finally able to see things neutrally and realistically. Your adopt a conciliatory attitude, which makes your partner regain their optimism and feel happy.\n\nTake advantage of this week, as your inventiveness will help you come up with solutions to problems that seemed insurmountable. Deal with any affairs that have so far been stagnant or hard to resolve. Changes will be positive, so do not stop them from happening. Even if you can not see it now, they are happening for a good reason. Be more practical and organized when it comes to your finances.]]></string>
    <string name="cancer_one">Salaried employees as well as businessmen will be blessed with opportunities.\n\nIndustries related to mechanical, automobiles and engineering show a lot of potential. Partnership ventures will have a lot of teething problems.\n\nStudents may opt to join professional courses with the objective of improving their career. Senior students going to colleges will need to quit their lethargy. Guidance from mentors will be important. Your attitude change and humble mannerisms will be appreciated by everybody. On a special occasion, a financial benefit from your in-laws is a probability. You will feel happy with the progress of your children. Barring a few ups and downs, your health will remain in topnotch. You may sometimes get an irritating or burning sensation in your body.\n\nExercising regularly will prove to be a boon. It is recommended that you conduct business and supply goods only against advance payments. Real estate deals will prove to be beneficial.</string>
    <string name="cancer_two">You can get closer to your loved ones and deal with your family affairs. The balance in your relationship may be disrupted, as you become more sensitive and prone to any change or comment. If you do not take everything personally, you will see that balance is more easily maintained. At the same time, your emotional resilience gives you the power you need to deal with difficult situations.\n\nThis week brings you the opportunity to come closer to your partner. Leave your insecurity behind in order to make time and space for more interesting things. This way, you will make your partner feel free. Make sure you show them your love and interest and do not resort to pettiness. Try to control your moodiness, because your partner is becoming tired of it. It is a pity to ruin the atmosphere with insignificant things.\n\nIn your work life, you are now ready to experience changes that will please you. Besides, the truth is that you have been considering some changes for a long time, or you are already working on them. So, act accordingly to make the most out of them. Relations between colleagues improve and you earn some important allies. Use this inclination for changes in your finances, as well. If this part of your life is stuck, you will certainly attempt some changes in order to get rid of the stress.</string>
    <string name="leo_one">Working environment for salaried employees will be pleasant. Businesses will thrive and see a phenomenal growth and progress! Those associated with the entertainment, decoration and cosmetic industry would do really well.\n\nFor students, availing admissions in colleges offering specialized courses could be difficult during this time. You will be able to clear all misunderstandings of the past with your friends. You will be pleased with the independent and positive outlook of your children. Their academic growth will also be very impressive. Your siblings will be brimming with love and respect for you! Your zest and vigour will help you cope with strenuous situations and workloads easily. Taking an occasional break will definitely do you good. No tasks, however hard to accomplish, will be physically challenging for you. In comparison to the previous week, your financial position is going to vastly improve. Trading in stocks and purchasing gold will certainly be profitable.</string>
    <string name="leo_two">Being vulnerable is something that you can control by using rational thinking. Avoid conflicts with those around you and do not add fuel to the fire in relationships that have been compromised. Around the middle of the week, you will regain your dynamism and your control over your life and your emotions. Unexpected changes will give you enthusiasm and optimism.\n\nThis week brings you a perfect opportunity to discuss some important issues with your partner. You may feel some exaggerated emotions or some insecurity that will make you seek reassurance from your partner. do not let these emotions ruin the warm atmosphere between you. You are a proud and generous person, so do not waste yourself on petty things. Enjoy honesty in your relationship and make sure you rise to the occasion.\n\nYour work routine is making you tired and bored. Repeating the same situations over and over is draining your patience, as nothing seems to be changing so far. All these negative things are about to end. Unexpected surprises boost some stagnant situations, while new discoveries will give you satisfaction regarding your attitude so far. Positive changes are ahead in your finances. Make the most of them without hesitation.</string>
    <string name="virgo_one">The week seems to be particularly lucrative for real estate contractors and those associated with the communication and telecom industry.\n\nSalaried employees may be offered either a salary raise or a promotion. Students will be able to concentrate better for the preparation of any competitive exams of their choice. There is a high probability of them doing extremely well in such exams! There is also a distinct possibility of you and your soulmate engaging in beautiful intimate moments. Love is in the air this week! Couples should refrain from entering into futile ego clashes with each other. Your overall health shall remain moderate during this time. Avoid eating junk or stale food. An upset stomach could not only disturb you physically but also mentally. Your physical discomforts shall ebb away during the weekend.\n\nYou will be blessed with a continuous source of financial income and your financial stability will be rock solid!</string>
    <string name="virgo_two">The only thing that makes you feel safe this week is the warm embrace of your family. You will try to get closer to your loved ones, to win their attention but also to devote your time to them. Your deeper instincts arise and determine your behavior. Your intuition is sharp and, if need be, it may save you from some difficult situations. You will regain your organization and discipline and you will be ready to face any trying situation.\n\nYour partner will be your harbor for the week. You will need to be close to them, in order to feel balance and calmness. Your instinct is strong and will help you deal with any sudden events in your love life. If you are single, this may lead you to a new relationship. Whatever the status of your love life, make sure you control the agitation that will arise between you and the person that interests you.\n\nMake sure you deal with pending obligations and plan your next steps. You can do so in a calm manner, maintaining self-control and a positive stance. Opportunities will arise during the week, marking the beginning of the changes you have been desiring for so long. Even in your finances, you will have the chance to set things straight and change them to your benefit.</string>
    <string name="libra_one">The week is very favourable for businessmen in the ice cream and beverage industry. The period is also exceptionally good for those in the education business.\n\nA change in job is a strong probability. Students will have no issues with regards to their level of focus and concentration. Students pursuing higher education will perform very well in their upcoming examinations. You will have complete and undivided cooperation from your beloved. You will be able to spend quality time with each other. Even the bond between your friends and family will be stronger than ever! You will always be smiling even in hectic and busy schedules. You will be able to fulfil all personal and business engagements without the slightest of fatigue. Since the inflow of income permits, it will be a very favourable time to consider making new investments.\n\nHasty financial decisions will definitely prove to be injurious in the long run.</string>
    <string name="libra_two">The time is right for you to deal with demanding situations, to attract attention and to intensify your persuasiveness through your warm and generous attitude. Expressing your creativity will not only give you practical solutions, but also help you get rid of your stress. You will feel a calmness that will help you enjoy life, away from the pressure of your daily routine.\n\nThis week, you must really try to overcome your emotional insecurities. Your partner may not feel up for fulfilling any demand of yours, solely in order to appease you insecurity. You focus on your relationship and you are willing to do your best to make it work.\n\nThis week you will need to devote time and effort to your collaborations, and, at the same time, defend your own work. You will be able to display your strengths, as well as the results of your efforts. The time is right for you to convince others of your strengths and to pursue satisfactory rewards on every level. This attitude is also beneficial for your finances. You have worked hard and you demand the raise you have been after.</string>
    <string name="scorpio_one">Today is very favourable for people associated with creative fields, performing arts and the entertainment industry.\n\nThe hard work and diligence of salaried employees will be duly noted. Students seeking admissions to reputed universities will be successful during this week. They will pass with flying colours in any interviews that they appear for! Students will also be successful in competitive examinations. You will be having a very special equation with your soulmate during this week. Blissful, romantic and intimate! Your parents will co-operate with you in every manner possible. People will be inspired by your energy levels and will look upon you as their role model! You will be able to comfortably and successfully fulfil all your personal and business obligations.\n\nIn all probability, you will be able to receive all pending dues from friends, family and business during this week. Wise investments made in the past will be profitable!</string>
    <string name="scorpio_two">You are quite likely to experience some of your deeper insecurities, ones related to the love you receive from your family or partner. You will seek their support and reassurance, in order to feel safe and confident. At the same time, you will be very communicative and articulate and the people around you will express their interest in your thoughts.\n\nYour week will be decent, provided that you overcome your extreme sensitivity. Near the weekend, you will be able to set an agenda of discussions regarding all the issues that keep you and your partner at a distance. Together, you will find solutions. This will make you feel relief and replenish your energy, so that the two of you can move forward together. Insight and successful communication will help you approach the person that interests you.\n\nAt work, make sure you use your communicative skills to engage in sales and commerce, if you are interested in those sectors. Through them, you will manage to set solid foundations that will improve your financial situation. Sudden changes work positively for you and your plans, professional and financial ones.</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_one">Businessmen associated with trading of stationery and printing materials will earn better profit margins. Businesses will be able to reach their desired turnover. Their profits will also substantially increase.\n\nArts and commerce students will have great coordination with their professors. They will remain attentive during class. This will positively reflect upon their results. Their excellent grades will pleasantly astonish one and all. Your siblings will help you to sort out some complicated issues. Atmosphere within the family will remain joyous and happy. The relations with your spouse will be blissful! You will easily be able to meet all your professional and personal obligations. You will exercise daily by going to the health club.\n\nNo wonder your health will remain in top-notch condition! Investments in stock, shares, bonds and speculative market will yield a healthy amount of profit. You will successfully be able to clear off all your pending debts including outstanding loans.</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_two"><![CDATA[You know exactly what you want and how to get it. Your resilience knows no end and it will get you where you need to go, despite the tiring effort. You have a great sense of optimism inside of you, which will make you active and energetic. Come Sunday, tensions subside and your relationships regain their stability. You will feel calmness in your soul.\n\nYou will experience an emotional turmoil that might stop you from thinking clearly. Moreover, this might make you have unreal expectations from your partner. In any case, the basis for your feelings is your fear, that arises and concerns the love and acceptance you get by your partner and you family. Make the most of your Sunday, when you will have the chance to smooth out any pending situations and bring back the harmony in your relationship.\n\nAt work, you will be able to display your many capabilities in order to achieve what your worth. You act with passion, optimism and enthusiasm, making the people around you feel safety and confidence with your actions and decisions. Sunday will be a day of rest and contemplation. Take advantage of your free time in order to think about your collaborations and to make decisions that will prove to be useful in the future. In your finances, pleasant changes are ahead of you.]]></string>
    <string name="capricorn_one">Salaried employees will need to be very careful with their behaviour at office. Despite working diligently and hard, their efforts will not be appreciated enough.\n\nAvoid arguing with superiors.The week seems to be quite promising for junior level for school going children. They will be able to make satisfactory progress. Your teachers and guides will support you wholeheartedly. You will feel closer to your partner than ever before during this week! The love you feel for each other shall be sheer poetry! Unmarried couples would witness great bonding and intimacy. You will need to take additional care of your health during the mid-week. You may be disturbed by some body ache. There is also a probability of suffering from mental stress.\n\nThere is every probability of you receiving financial help from your siblings or friends when you need it the most. You will be instantaneously relieved from all negative stress.</string>
    <string name="capricorn_two">You will be able to take advantage of upcoming opportunities. You are going through an inventive phase, thus the time Is right for you to deal with annoying situations and move on. You need to put some effort into things, as being favored by the universe is not enough. Unexpected changes will help you achieve your goals and move forward, even if this means you have to act in a subversive manner.\n\nEmotions will be intense in your personal life. You will become more vulnerable, which could be expressed either through insecurity or through excess display of affection. Do not suffocate your partner with your fears and do not become manipulative. Talk to your partner, express your thoughts and find solutions to the issues that trouble your relationship. If you are single, it is better if you do not move on to something new these days, as your judgment is a bit cloudy.\n\nThis will be a very good week for you. If you manage to control your feelings and to keep calm, you will have strength and the will to succeed at whatever it is you are working on. The end of the week will bring you the opportunity to sort out your obligations, so that you can finally stop feeling lost amongst them. You need better planning when it comes to your finances.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_one">You are likely to take up a few new projects on hand. Although, you may face several difficulties along the way. Finishing the projects within the stipulated timeline will be a challenge.\n\nStudents, roll up your sleeves, straighten your posture and get ready to work! The planets do not seem to be supportive, but there is nothing hard work cannot accomplish. If you use harsh words, one thing will lead to another and you will eventually end up having fierce arguments with your partner. The repercussions will be extremely severe. Avoid junk food and stick to nutritious meals as there is a probability of facing minor digestive disorders. Symptoms like common cold, cough and sore throat should be treated with immediate effect.Planetary influence during this week will lure you to take unnecessary risks.\n\nDo not fall for such traps! Taking unnecessary risks will certainly have adverse results. Be careful and play it safe!</string>
    <string name="aquarius_two">There is a generalized excitement, constant action and a lot of courage. You are enthusiastic and your energy makes you move constantly and forcefully. Make sure you take a pause when necessary, especially during conversations, as you are likely to make mistakes that could get you in trouble.\n\nIn your love life, it is quite likely that you will somehow revisit your past. A person from your past comes back to your life or your thoughts. This will not be a problem, so long as you maintain control and balance. Be careful, lest you get carried away and you end up ruining everything you have worked for. In short, if you are in a relationship, do not let it get affected but an old acquaintance. If you are single, think twice before you decide to go back to the past, no matter how safe that would make you feel.\n\nAt work, your week will be successful and dynamic. You can now build collaborations that are strong and enduring, but you will have to act with self-control and strength. Make the most of the end of the week, in order to sort out your obligations and your collaborations and to deal with pending affairs. Do the same for your finances, so that things start to improve for you.</string>
    <string name="pisces_one">You will receive complete co-operation from your superiors and colleagues at work. The week is favourable for business expansion.\n\nManagers and administrators will be required to go that extra mile! This is an excellent week for students. They would have maximum focus and concentration upon their academics. Students will have an intense desire to expand the horizons of their knowledge. The period will prove to be slightly on the harsher side for married couples. Whatever you say may be misconstrued by your partner. Control your anger and refrain from harsh words. Ailments of the stomach and gastric disorders are a distinct probability during this time. Light exercises will help you stay physically fit. Spare at least ten minutes every day for meditation.\n\nThere is a distinct possibility of incurring expenses towards travels; or purchasing decorative items for your residence. You will be able to repay any bank loans that you had availed.</string>
    <string name="pisces_two">You feel an emotional imbalance and you seek the warmth and support of your family, in order to regain your strength and feel confident again. Do not isolate yourself, if you wish to maintain control. Be straight-forward to those who care for you and you shall come up with solutions to the issues that trouble you. You will have the strength to change your life. Any unexpected changes that might occur will work to your favor.\n\nThis week has the potential to be calm, so long as you remain honest with your partner. There will be moments when you will need them by your side in order to gain some emotional balance. Talk to them and do not conceal this need of yours by behaving in an abrupt, moody and annoying manner.\n\nThis will be smooth, as long as you use your communicative skills for the benefit of your collaborations. Handle your emotional instability and do not let it harm your professional relationships and decisions. Make good use of any sudden changes in order for your finances to improve.</string>
    <string name="lbl_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="txt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="txt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="lbl_keep_me_logged_in">Keep me logged in</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_create_account">Not account yet?</string>
    <string name="lbl_network_error">Internet Connectivity Error!</string>
    <string name="lbl_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="rd_user_name">username required</string>
    <string name="rd_password">password required</string>
    <string name="lbl_signup">SIGNUP</string>
    <string name="txt_full_name">Name</string>
    <string name="txt_user_email">Email</string>
    <string name="txt_user_password">Password</string>
    <string name="lbl_by_pressing_cont">By using this application, you agree to the</string>
    <string name="lbl_pravicy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="rd_full_name">name required</string>
    <string name="rd_email">email required</string>
    <string name="re_password">password required</string>
</resources>
